domo.com 2016-12-01

# Domo Privacy Policy | Domo

## Scope of this Policy

Domo understands you care how information about you is collected and used. Domo is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who interact with us. This Domo Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes Domo, Inc. and its affiliated entities (collectively “Domo”) privacy practices for our websites, services, and apps that link to this policy. This policy also details our privacy practices related to Domo marketing, advertising, and company events.

The Domo Business Cloud is an online business management platform. We provide the Domo Business Cloud and related support, consulting, and other services to our customers. In this Privacy Policy, we will refer to the Domo Business Cloud and related services collectively as our "Services." We will refer to our emails, newsletters, and other marketing and advertising practices collectively as our “Communications.”

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

### Domo Services

We provide Services to our customers. As part of the Services, customer data may be stored on our computer systems. As our customer, when you use our Services to process data you have collected, you control the data you collect, what data is uploaded to the Services, and how that data is used. The collection, use, transfer, and retention of customer data in our Services are governed by our customer’s privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy. As a data processor, we will cooperate with you in your efforts to control your data.

## Information Collected by Domo

### Domo registration and customer support

You may provide us with information about you when you complete a Domo web form, register to use a Domo website (such as www.domo.com) or Service, request a Services demonstration, respond to an advertisement, contact Domo for support or other offerings, or attend an event or forum in which Domo is hosting or participating. During such processes, we collect Personal Information about you. For example, we may collect your name, company name, address, email, phone number, billing and payment information, position, or title. We may also collect other public and third party information about you to supplement your profile, such as public information about the company where you work.

### Domo websites and use of Cookies

We receive and store certain information about how you use our websites and Services when you visit a Domo website or use our Services. For example, we receive information that your browser or device sends to our servers whenever you visit a Domo website. Your browser or device may tell us your internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, computer and connection information such as browser type, version, language and time zone settings, browser plug-in types, operating system, and type of device you are using. When you visit a Domo website, your browser may also tell us information such as the actions you take on our website, the page that led you to our website and, if applicable, the search terms you typed into a search engine that led you to our website.

We may receive information about how you use our websites and Services through the use of first-party and third-party cookies, and also web beacons and other similar technologies. Our servers collect similar information when you are logged into our website or Services. The information we receive through cookies and similar technologies may be associated with you, depending on the website or Services you are using, and whether you have provided information identifying yourself to the website or Services.

In addition, third parties may be able to collect information about your online activities when you use our websites or Services using cookies or other technologies. We do not respond to web browser ‘do not track’ signals or other similar transmissions that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who visit our websites or who use our websites or Services.

### Buttons, tools, and content from other companies

Domo websites and Services may include buttons, tools, or content that link to other companies' services (for example, a Facebook "Like" button). We may collect information about your use of these features. In addition, when you see or interact with these buttons, tools, or content, or view a Domo web page containing them, some information from your browser may automatically be sent to the other company. Please read that company's privacy policy for more information regarding its use of that information.

### Domo social networking pages

We maintain pages on many social networking sites. We may collect information when you interact with our social networking pages.

### Domo online advertising

We advertise online, including displaying Domo ads across the Internet on websites and in apps. When we advertise online to you, we may collect information about which ads are displayed to you, which ads you click on, and the web page where the ad was displayed to you.

### Public chat, message boards and user postings

You might provide Personal Information through your public participation in chat sessions, message boards, user communities associated with our Services (such as Domo Dojo), blogs, email exchanges, or newsgroups on our websites. That information may be available to anyone who has access to the website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you make generally available through such websites.

## Use of the information collected by Domo

We may use the information we collect about you to:

  * Provide you Domo website content and Services, as well as any other services, support, or information you have requested
  * Operate and improve our websites and Services, and diagnose related problems
  * Personalize our website, Services, and Communications to your likely interests and needs
  * Send you business messages such as those related to Services notifications, payments or renewal of your subscription
  * Send you information about Domo, new releases, special offers, and similar marketing information
  * Conduct market research about our customers, their interests, and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns
  * Display personalized ads to you
  * Combine information we collect about you with other public or private information sources in order to provide you with Communications that may be relevant to you and to enhance the Services we provide to you
  * Contact you via telephone to discuss our Services and related offers with you
  * Aggregate data from our Services used for benchmarking and to improve our Services.

Where required under applicable law, we will obtain your consent to the use of your Personal Information for marketing purposes.

### Newsletter subscription information

From time to time, we may provide information to our customers and potential customers in the form of electronic or print newsletters. When you subscribe to our newsletter you may be added to our mailing list and will receive announcements and information about Domo. It will be emailed or mailed to the address that you provide when you subscribe.

### Domo text messages

Our Services may allow us and other Services users to periodically communicate with you through text messaging. We may contact you regarding the Services we provide to you, such as providing system alerts. You may manage your contact information and notification preferences in your Services account settings.

## Sharing information collected by Domo

We work with companies that help us run our business. These companies may provide services such as delivering customer support, processing and collecting payments, and sending Communications on our behalf. These companies may have access to your Personal Information as required to help us run our business.

Domo may also share your Personal Information:

  * When you have consented to the sharing
  * With our affiliated companies
  * When you purchase a license to use a or indicate interest in a third party product or service through Domo, so the third party may contact you about your purchase or interest
  * With our resellers and other sales partners
  * When we are required or believe we are required to provide information in response to a subpoena, court order, applicable law, government statute, regulation or other legal process
  * When we have a good faith belief that the disclosure is necessary to prevent or respond to fraud, defend our websites or Services against attacks, or protect the property and security of Domo, or the property and security of our customers and users
  * To the extent necessary to meet lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements
  * If we merge with or are acquired by another company, we sell a website, app, or business unit, or all or a substantial portion of our assets are acquired by another company, in which case your information may be one of the assets that is transferred
  * When we hire companies to help us market our websites and Services and provide you with information and offers related to Domo, including displaying ads to you across the Internet
  * When we enlist the services of participating third party carriers to provide messaging services
  * When we aggregate and share de-identified information collected by our Services in order to provide statistical information or market research to third parties

Within the Domo Business Cloud Appstore, our customers can request and obtain access to software applications that are developed and supported by third party providers. We refer to these applications as Non-Domo Apps. If you install or enable a Non-Domo App for use with the Domo Business Cloud, we will allow the provider of the Non-Domo App to access your data as required for the interoperation of the Non-Domo App with the Domo Business Cloud. We are not responsible for the use, disclosure, modification, or deletion of your data by a Non-Domo App provider resulting from your use of a Non-Domo App. Please read the Non-Domo App Provider’s privacy policy and Non-Domo App license terms for more information regarding its use of your data in the Non-Domo App.

## Information security and storage

We understand that the security of your Personal Information is important. We implement reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security controls designed to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, despite our efforts, no security controls are completely effective and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of your Personal Information.

Your Personal Information and data files are stored on our servers and the servers of our affiliated companies and companies we hire to provide services to us.

## Cross-border data transfers

Your Personal Information may be stored in the United States, or transferred to other countries where the companies we hire to help us run our business are located, such as Australia, India, Japan, South Africa, and the United Kingdom. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your Personal Information, we will protect it as described in this privacy policy.

Domo adheres to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework regarding Personal Information transferred from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to Domo, Inc. in the U.S., as described in our Privacy Shield Privacy Policy. To learn more about the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and to view our certification, please visit [www.privacyshield.gov.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome)

Domo also maintains an affirmative commitment to the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework, which is not affected by our participation in the Privacy Shield. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification, please visit [safeharbor.export.gov/swisslist.aspx](https://safeharbor.export.gov/swisslist.aspx)

## Reviewing, updating or deleting your Personal Information

We take reasonable steps intended to ensure that your Personal Information we collect is accurate, complete, and current by using the most recent information provided to us. Our websites and Services may allow you to review and edit your Personal Information by accessing your profile or similar feature of the website or Service you are using. For our websites, you may have the ability to manage your cookies and similar technologies through your web browser settings. You should consult the settings and instructions provided by the provider of your web browser for more information.

You may also submit a request to us to review, edit, or delete your Personal Information by emailing your request to [privacy@domo.com](mailto:privacy@domo.com), or if you prefer, you can contact us through physical mail at Domo, Inc., 772 East Utah Valley Drive American Fork, Utah 84003 (Attn:  Privacy Office), or by telephone at 1.800.899.1000. Our business hours for telephone contact are 9:00 AM to 5:00 PM Mountain. Once we verify your identify, we will assist you with your request.

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to provide you with the websites and Services you use, as needed to comply with our legal obligations or enforce our agreements. For example, we may retain certain records for legal or internal business reasons, such as fraud prevention. Some of your information may also remain on backup systems after your use of our websites and Services ends.

You can choose not to provide us with your Personal Information, but if you do not provide us with your Personal Information when we request it, we may not be able to provide you with the websites and Services you use, or tailor them to you.

## Opting-out of Domo Communications

You may opt out of receiving Communications by modifying your website or Service profile, or by unsubscribing to the marketing mailings or newsletters you no longer desire. To unsubscribe, please submit your information through http://www.domo.com/unsubscribe, or follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions that are contained within the mailing, newsletter or other Communication that we send to you. You may also send an email to [privacy@domo.com](mailto:privacy@domo.com) with "Unsubscribe" in the body, together with a description of the Communications you no longer desire to receive.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may change or update this Privacy Policy to allow us to use or share your Personal Information in a materially different way. For new users, such changes will become effective upon posting. For existing users, the changes and updates will become effective 30 days after posting.  We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Questions or concerns

If you have any questions related to this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@domo.com](mailto:privacy@domo.com).

x

Domo requests your consent to send you email communications. Please customize your Domo experience:

**YES** \- Send email

**NO** \- Do not send email

By selecting "YES" and clicking "Submit", you agree that Domo, Inc. and its representatives may contact you at the email address provided. You may unsubscribe, or view our Privacy Policy, at any time.
